{
    "data":[
   {
        "Question" :"Cốt truyện",
        "Choice" : ["Pure","Thorny","Plot","Poisonous"],
        "CorrectAns": "Plot",
        "Pronunciation":"/plɑːt/"
    },
    {
        "Question" : "Bối cảnh",
        "Choice" : ["Background","Produce","Release","Screen"],
        "CorrectAns": "Background",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈbæk.ɡraʊnd/"
    },
    {
        "Question" : "Diễn viên chính",
        "Choice" : ["Main actor","Plot","Pollution","Solar panel"],
        "CorrectAns": "Main actor",
        "Pronunciation":"/meɪn ˈæk.tɚ/"
    },
    {
        "Question" : "Nhân vật",
        "Choice" : ["Trailer","Character","Shortage","Solar panel"],
        "CorrectAns": "Character",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈker.ək.tɚ/"
    },
    {
        "Question" : "Nhà làm phim",
        "Choice" : ["Emissions","Movie maker","Release","Director"],
        "CorrectAns": "Movie maker",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈmuː.viˌmeɪ.kɚ/"
    },
    {
        "Question" : "Đạo diễn",
        "Choice" : ["Woodland","Director","Release","Solar panel"],
        "CorrectAns": "Director",
        "Pronunciation":"/daɪˈrek.tɚ/"
    },
    {
        "Question" : "Nhà phê bình phim",
        "Choice" : ["Cast","Solar panel","Film critic","Soil erosion"],
        "CorrectAns": "Film critic",
        "Pronunciation":"/fɪlm ˈkrɪt̬.ɪk/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Nhà biên kịch",
        "Choice" : ["Contamination","Director","Scriptwriter","Polluter"],
        "CorrectAns": "Scriptwriter",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈskrɪptˌraɪ.t̬ɚ/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Kinh dị",
        "Choice" : ["Gas exhaust","Action","Horror","Historical"],
        "CorrectAns": "Horror",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈhɔːr.ɚ/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Cổ trang",
        "Choice" : ["Historical","Drama","Release","Cartoon"],
        "CorrectAns": "Historical",
        "Pronunciation":"/hɪˈstɔːr.ɪ.kəl/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Hoạt Hình",
        "Choice" : ["Cartoon","Gangster","War","Polluter"],
        "CorrectAns": "Cartoon",
        "Pronunciation":"/kɑːrˈtuːn/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Phim hài",
        "Choice" : ["Comedy","emission","Sitcom","Soil erosion"],
        "CorrectAns": "Comedy",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈkɑː.mə.di/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Phim hình sự",
        "Choice" : ["Crime Film","War Film","Tragedy","Horror"],
        "CorrectAns": "Crime Film",
        "Pronunciation":"/kraɪm fɪlm/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Bi kịch",
        "Choice" :["Tragedy","Drama","Deforestation","Musical"],
        "CorrectAns": "Tragedy",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈtrædʒ.ə.di/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Rạp chiếu phim",
        "Choice" : ["Emissions","Excessive","release","Cinema"],
        "CorrectAns": "Cinema",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈsɪn.ə.mə/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Thuyết minh, lồng tiếng",
        "Choice" : ["Curb","Preservation","Dubbed","Over-abuse"],
        "CorrectAns": "Dubbed",
        "Pronunciation":"/dʌbd/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Máy chiếu phim",
        "Choice" : ["Gas exhaust","Catalyze","Dispose","Projector"],
        "CorrectAns": "Projector",
        "Pronunciation":"/prəˈdʒek.tɚ/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Phụ đề",
        "Choice" : ["Woodland","Ecosystem","Habitats","Subtitles"],
        "CorrectAns": "Subtitles",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈsʌbˌtaɪ.t̬əl/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Phim bom tấn",
        "Choice" : ["Endangered","Ecosystem","Pollutant","Blockbuster"],
        "CorrectAns": "Blockbuster",
        "Pronunciation":"/ˈblɑːkˌbʌs.tɚ/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Tấm vé",
        "Choice" : ["Gas exhaust","Ticket","Dispose","Traitor"],
        "CorrectAns": "Ticket",
        "Pronunciation":"/tɪk.ɪt/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Chỗ ngồi",
        "Choice" : ["Woodland","Seat","Erosion","Thriller"],
        "CorrectAns": "Seat",
        "Pronunciation":"/sit/"
    },{
        
            "Question" : "Người nổi tiếng",
            "Choice" : ["Erosion","Catalyze","Celebrities","Projector"],
            "CorrectAns": "Celebrities",
            "Pronunciation":"/səˈlɛbrɪtiz/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Phim hình sự",
        "Choice" : ["Crime Film","War Film","Tragedy","Horror"],
        "CorrectAns": "Crime Film",
        "Pronunciation":"/kraɪm fɪlm/"
    },{
        "Question" : "Hãng sản xuất phim",
        "Choice" : ["Historical","Drama","Entertainment","Cartoon"],
        "CorrectAns": "Entertainment",
        "Pronunciation":"/en.t̬ɚˈteɪn.mənt/"
    },{
        "Question" :"Bắp rang/Bỏng ngô",
        "Choice" : ["Pure","Popcorn","Plot","Poisonous"],
        "CorrectAns": "Popcorn",
        "Pronunciation":"/pɑːp.kɔːrn/"
       
    }]
  
}


